Privacy Policy
==============

At Declutter The Mind, accessible from https://declutterthemind.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Declutter The Mind and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to [contact](https://declutterthemind.com/contact-us/).

Log Files
---------

Declutter The Mind follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

Cookies and Web Beacons
-----------------------

Like any other website, Declutter The Mind uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

Google Analytics
----------------

Declutter The Mind uses Google Analytics and cookies to track website traffic and visitor activity. This helps us better understand our visitors. The data is only collected in Google Analytics and is not shared with third-parties.

Email
-----

If you choose to subscribe to our email list, you consent to our privacy policy. We collect emails to an email list using MailChimp, to broadcast newsletter emails to our subscribers. We do not share or sell this information.

Children’s Information
----------------------

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Declutter The Mind does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

Online Privacy Policy Only
--------------------------

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Declutter The Mind. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

Consent
-------

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

Data deletion
-------------

Users may request to have their personal data deleted at any time. To do so, [please contact us and submit a ticket](https://help.declutterthemind.com/submit_ticket) requesting we delete your data. All your data will be deleted upon request.

Share this:
